// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "We … to the school together",
    answer: "Go",
    options: ["Going", "Go", "Goes", "Went"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "… Lizzie eat fish?",
    answer: "Does",
    options: ["Does", "Do", "Doing", "Did"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The children … at playground",
    answer: "Are",
    options: ["Is", "Am", "Are", "Do"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Mathematics … so hard",
    answer: "Is",
    options: ["Is", "Are", "That", "Was"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "… you …. Me?",
    answer: "Do, Love",
    options: ["Did, love", "Do, Loves", "Doing, Love", "Do, Love"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "She … to work",
    answer: "Walks",
    options: ["Walk", "Walking", "Walked", "Walks"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A: Do you like to cook? B: ...",
    answer: "Yes, I like to cook",
    options: [
      "Yes, I likes to cook",
      "Yes, I liked to cook",
      "Yes, I like to cook",
      "Yes, I am liking to cook",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A: How do you go to the office? B:...",
    answer: "I ride the car to the office",
    options: [
      "I ride the car to the office",
      "I rode the car to the office",
      "I riding the car to the office",
      "I ridden the car to the office",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Q: When do you do your homework? R:...",
    answer: "I do my homework at 6 PM",
    options: [
      "I have did my homework at 6 PM",
      "I did my homework at 6 PM",
      "I do my homework at 6 PM",
      "I am doing my homework at 6 PM",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Q: Does he love his mother Y:...",
    answer: "He loves his mother",
    options: [
      "He love his mother",
      "He loves his mother",
      "He to love his mother",
      "He is loving his mother",
    ],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
